I have always been in love with you
Of course I will always be with you
You know that, you know
I will always be with you
I will never be with you
I'm the one who's holding the hand
The time when the light shines
The smile of the wind is shining
You, you, you, you
If you love me, I'll be able to stand by your side
I'll be able to stand by your side
Mokomuka!
Matsuri! Mokomuka!
Hmm, that's good.
It's been a week since Mokomuka arrived.
Mokomuka!
Mokomuka, are you okay?
What are you doing?
I'm going to take a shower.
I want to take a shower too.
It's not too far from Uiba.
That's what I like.
It's all for the sake of everyone.
If I go in, I'll fall asleep and fall asleep.
That's right.
It's been a year since I first started.
I was quite scared when I was young.
But I like it because it's cool.
I'm so excited.
I know how I feel, but I'm not young.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Uiba wants to see Uiba.
You're not.
What?
I don't want to be angry with you.
I'm angry.
What?
Are you angry?
It's been a year since I first started.
What?
It's a fake.
You said you were going to be a fake.
What?
I'm going to be a fake.
You said you were going to be a fake.
I'm not.
I was looking at the ticket for the next door.
I can't get in the next door.
Okay.
There are three seconds left.
That restaurant is very close to the door.
And this year, I'm going to be a fake.
I'm going to be a fake.
I'm going to be a fake too.
It's impossible.
No, I'm going to be a fake.
Oh!
Muka Muka!
Dad!
dangerous!
Muka Muka!
Stop it!
It's dangerous!
Muka Muka!
I'm sorry.
I was going to be a fake.
What?
It's a joke.
Misebao, what are you doing?
Yono is doing it.
What?
You were going to be a fake.
I thought you could be a fake.
That's good.
Eun 안녕하세요.
Yono, you're dangerous.
I'm sorry.
You were going to be a fake.
No matter what happens to me,
I'll never be ugly again.
It's not right.
Now that you're doing it.
You're doing it.
I'm doing it.
I'll never be ugly.
No matter what happens to me,
You're doing it.
This is good.
It's no good for your head, right?
Let's go!
I knew it!
It's not good!
If I were to pick it up, no one would do it.
Hey, Doku!
You're right.
Hey, look at that.
Look at the mirror.
I told you to go back to the shop.
If you're worried about that, you can go back to your own shop.
What are you talking about?
Are you ready to go to the shop?
I'm not going to do my job.
That's right.
Let's go!
Wait!
Don't you think it's a good idea to go back to the shop?
It's my son.
Yes.
It's so expensive.
It's the smell of history.
This store is made by Ed.
Is it Ed?
My father, G.
And his mother-in-law.
This store has a price.
Everyone in town is looking for it.
This store is...
Yes.
I'm sure I'll win this year.
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not.
I'm a human being in town.
I'm so happy that you came to the shop.
But I'm not going to go to the shop.
I'm not going.
It's a bad idea to go to the shop.
That's why you can stay there for a long time.
This store is closed for a long time.
Not good.
That's too bad.
How is it possible?
What do you think it is?
What the hell?
I think it's hard to believe it's a little useful.
What is it that can't be helped?
You have to do it.
Don't do it to me.
No, I'm so tough.
I'm a human.
You're a human.
A human.
Look!
You're a man.
What are you doing?
Ah! If I had gone too far, I would have been able to go to Yoppodokini.
Ah! Nikudango was born in 2,000 years.
Well, I'll think about what's going on in the future.
Father, come to read it.
It's from Ban Gohan.
Yes!
Eat everything!
Oh
dear
They said you could put them in the bag.
Oh!
one last time
You're absolutely right!
Eat!
paschua
Yes.
Yes, Jumiko's usual His Majesty!
ah
Yes, I got it!
You look like you're waiting for me.
Are you all right?
I was surprised.
I'm so scared.
Do you understand?
What's the difference between you and me?
I was surprised.
Do you also want to win over me?
Yes, but I don't know.
I don't know yet.
It's hard for me to be an adult.
That's not what I meant.
I'll definitely win over you.
I don't know anything about you.
What did you come here for?
Oh, right.
My mom was a rice cooker.
I like to practice rice with rice.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared that I won't be able to win over you.
I'm so scared.
What's going on?
Please come here.
I'm so scared.
Is this really going to be a dead body?
Yes, I understand.
Hey, here it is.
What's the matter?
Is the shots going to be that dead body?
Well, that's because of your delusion.
I'm getting dizzy.
You mean you're so dead?
My mom said that Kami-sama was feeling down.
She was in her blood.
I was so lucky to be able to do it for my own good.
As I thought,
I was able to take my horse from the old town from the old town.
But since I was a kid,
I was able to take my horse from the old town.
I'm sure I'm going to take my horse from now on.
I don't think this is the right place for you, Mr. Arisama.
Ui-baa!
You know, the superman who's going to do the carnival today...
Carnival?
Yes. That's why he's here.
Look.
Nice!
What the hell is this?
Ah! I'm glad you're here!
Oganki!
What?
Goethe!
I heard it!
That ninja's head is a pig!
It's a pig!
It's a pig's head!
Even if it's not a pig's head, it's a carnival from this year.
If you come here at night, it's good.
It's a pig's head!
Isn't it a little too much?
That's right!
It's just a pig that doesn't look like a pig!
It's too much!
It's a pig's head!
What's a carnival?
Don't say anything!
It's a little bit of a pig's head!
Great!
And the troublemaker is planting some palm trees inside!
Huh?
Whimpinged Sakai Morobi!
Oh, I see.
I see.
Hello, Muka Muka!
You're really cool!
I know you're doing this!
Muka Muka!
Muka!
Wow!
Nice!
Amazing!
Oh no!
Wait!
Are you okay?
What are you eating?
I don't know what I'm eating.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Yes! Yes!
I'm sorry.
Sanpei!
I'm eating.
Oh no!
What's wrong, dad?
Is the wind still nice?
It's nice. I don't think Matsuri will die.
Is it the death of the ghost?
The ghost is still alive.
Everyone was angry tomorrow, but I don't know what to do.
I'm not going anywhere.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I'm going to die tomorrow.
I have no time to do this.
I don't know what you're going to do.
I'm going to get you all to die tomorrow.
I'm going to die tomorrow.
That's right, Senta-kun.
It's because everyone is doing their best to teach Kami-sama how to do it.
That's what I was told to you.
Kami-sama, did you know about that?
That's why I was so worried about you.
I don't know if you know about it.
Kama-kun.
I want to die, too.
But it's not a good thing.
Everyone, you have a carnival in front of you.
Okay.
Please don't do that.
Please.
Carnival.
Yes.
Is it a festival?
No.
Oh, it's a festival.
I want to have a festival in front of you.
It's not like everyone has a festival.
I want to play with it, too.
Kami-sama, let's have a festival.
I tried to save him.
If you failed, you would be in trouble.
He could have been killed by the boss, right?
That's right.
He was killed by the boss who killed the boss.
He really sprayed a lot.
Now, I can be the boss.
What about you, master?
What you said?
Teacher, it's so short.
I'm back!
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka Muka!
I thought you'd do it!
I can do it right now!
Alright!
I'll do it right away!
I'm sorry.
I can't do anything.
Go away!
It's better than a year old this year so I won't leave you.
Alright.
You should be able to transform it.
Let's keep hearing it.
It's not over yet.
Huh?!
Let's go!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
I did it!
Dokun!
Thank you!
Let's go!
I'm so happy!
It's so cool!
I can't get out of here!
Why is this so funny?
Let's go!
Translated by Releska
That's right, I always have that feeling
When I hear your voice, I hear your voice
It's a strange thing, it's a strange thing
as long as they can be seen
the eyes of the stars are Hi-Ha-To
Because of it
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
The answer creates a silhouette
It's so nice! So nice! So nice! So nice!
The silhouette
creates a silhouette
that you can't enjoy
The story is about to be forgotten.
Hello, Miro!
I'm Torida!
I'm HIKOKI, I'm KyouRi!
Oh, no.
Why?
Aren't you going to stop me?
I'm your friend, Jarlmash.
Boop! Boop! Boop! Boop!
You're nothing but a monster.
I see.
Alright, I'll try my best!
Next time, I'll do my best!
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!